{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","address":"2111 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48203","owner":"TSFR Apple Venture LLC","licenseNumber":"082195","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":null,"establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000148F5F3331C554C09853320845394540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44445","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","inspectionDate":"2018-12-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44445","inspectionDate":"12/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"44445","inspectionDate":"12/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Over Oven (convection)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"44445","inspectionDate":"12/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Next to the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"42496","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","inspectionDate":"2018-05-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42496","inspectionDate":"5/25/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"42496","inspectionDate":"5/25/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40570","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","inspectionDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40570","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Utensil(s) knives","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Knives","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"40570","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Beverage Dispenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"40570","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"inspectionid":"40570","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"5-203.14","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be installed to preclude backflow of contaminants into the water supply system at each point of use at the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT by providing an air gap or installing an APPROVED backflow prevention device. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow prevention","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Under the Dipper well","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"inspectionid":"40570","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at 30 inches above the floor","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"40570","inspectionDate":"10/25/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at 30 inches above the floor","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"38408","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","inspectionDate":"2017-03-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38408","inspectionDate":"3/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"38408","inspectionDate":"3/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"38408","inspectionDate":"3/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"38408","inspectionDate":"3/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"38408","inspectionDate":"3/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"38408","inspectionDate":"3/24/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in water","subProblem":"That is standing","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use cool, running water with enough flow to remove particles."}]},{"inspectionid":"36995","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","inspectionDate":"2016-11-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36995","inspectionDate":"11/3/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In prep area","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"inspectionid":"36995","inspectionDate":"11/3/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"36995","inspectionDate":"11/3/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Faucet","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"36995","inspectionDate":"11/3/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4475","name":"Applebee's #7833","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Drip Tray","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4475"}}